William Tjang

Email: william.tj29@gmail.com **Website:** https://twillij.github.io/

I am a Sydney-based developer who specialises in game development. I have 3 years of programming experience with C# and C++ and have applied them using Unity and Unreal Engine, and have recently shipped a product as the lead publishing developer.

Technical Skills

Programming C++, C#, HTML/CSS

Game Engine Unreal Engine, Unity

Game Development UI/UX, camera work, physics simulation, optimisation, porting, VR

Version Control Git, including GitHub/GitLab and SourceTree

Project Management Trello, HacknPlan, ClickUp

MS Office Word, Excel, PowerPoint, Outlook

Auxiliary Skills

Technical support

Customer service

Teaching

• Multilingual (English, Indonesian,

Japanese)

Problem solving

Communication

Teamwork

Leadership

Self-motivated

Professional Experience

Unreal Engine C++ Programmer @ Blowfish Studios

Sep 2021 – Present

I develop video game projects as well as help other developers publish their games using Unreal Engine and C++, which are then released on various platforms such as Steam, PlayStations, Xboxes and Nintendo consoles.

Game Design Workshop Instructor @ Dr Egg Adventures

Jun 2021 - Jul 2021

Taught primary schoolers on game design basics using various apps through Zoom

IT Support Staff @ National Institute of Dramatic Arts (NIDA)

Oct 2019 - Oct 2020

Served as level 1 & 2 IT support for students and staffs within the Kensington campus

Finance Officer @ Rider & Bell Group

Jul 2018 - Oct 2019

Performed various financial affairs tasks including general bookkeeping, service delivery management and purchasing management, along with occasional tasks such as low-level IT support and website maintenance

Private Tutor @ Ezy Math Tutoring

Dec 2016 - Dec 2018

Worked as a contractor for a tutoring agency during which I prepared my own content

Education

Academy of Interactive Entertainment

2019 - 2020

Advanced Diploma of Game Programming

University of New South Wales

2014 - 2018

Bachelor of Economics

Caringbah High School

2008 - 2013

Higher School Certificate

Referees

Rick Ko Venkat Ravilla

Project Lead Systems Architect, ICT manager

JBK Studios National Institute of Dramatic Arts (NIDA)

Contact details are available upon request